ipraxa.com 2019-06-06

# iPraxa Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

At iPraxa, we understand how vital privacy is to our clients and visitors, and therefore we strive to be crystal clear about how we collect, use, disclose and store your personal information. Please note that whenever you visit, see, use and communicate with iPraxa.com from a computer, mobile phone, tablet, TV, or any other device, you accept to this privacy policy along with our Terms & Conditions mentioned on our website www.iPraxa.com.

Hence, it is important that you read our Privacy Policy carefully because whenever you log in to our website, you consent to our information practices described in the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy, you should not access and use our website and Services. Please review the following carefully to understand what happens to any personal information that we collect from you, or that you voluntarily provide to us.

### Collection of Information

WWhenever you access or use our website iPraxa.com, we may collect and store the below-mentioned information about you:

  * Why you’re visiting our website? - Your purpose about the use of our website. Such information may include your personal data, location data, communication data and traffic data.
  * Information that you voluntarily supply to us either while on the website or in responding, via email or any other medium, to a feature provided on the website.
  * Any other information that you provide to us either voluntarily or automatically.

**Please Note:** We DO NOT collect or store any kind of payment-related information, including your Bank Account or Credit and Debit Card details while processing payments on our website.

### Usage of Collected Information

We may use the information collected from you to improve our services and customize your experience on our website. Additionally, we may also use the information for other purposes, like:

  * To quickly provide you with any information you request from us related to our services
  * To notify you about any changes to our website and services
  * To allow our website to remember your personal preferences, such as what sections of our website you visit frequently and your user ID
  * To conduct research on users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our users
  * To measure the use of our website, to improve the content of our site and to deliver tailored advertisements
  * To be in compliance with all applicable laws
  * To provide advice and purchase recommendations
  * To respond to your questions, have efficient communication and to provide you with efficient customer service
  * For marketing and promotional purposes, such as sending you newsletters, special offers, and promotions if you have opted to receive them.
  * To contact you about our services which we think may interest you, or if a problem arises.

Additionally, if you have ever previously shown your interest in our services, we may send you the information and details of our new and upcoming services. And, if you have given your consent in advance, then only we authorize the selected third parties to use your details to provide you with the information related to our services. However, you shall always have an option to withdraw the consent anytime. In case you decide not to supply or provide us with certain information, we may not be able to provide you with some services that are dependent on the collection of this information.

### Sharing of Information

We do not sell, rent, trade or disclose end users’ personal or identifying information to any third parties or person except our employees or business partners which are required to provide support or services. However, to make our website and services more valuable to our clients and visitors, we may share the generic aggregated data, which is not related to the identification of personal information relating to any one individual, with our trusted affiliates, business partners/subsidiaries and advertisers for the marketing and promotional purposes, not with any other unauthorized third-party/entity.

We will not disclose any personal information that we collect online from you to allow third parties to use such information to email promotional offers directly to you unless you have permitted us to disclose such information for the purposes of receiving promotional offers from such third parties.

### Links to Third Party Websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to our website, www.iPraxa.com. Sometimes, we may provide links to third party websites, which we believe you may be interested in and whose privacy policies are separate from this Privacy Policy, on our website. And, even we may include links of third parties on the website but that does not inevitably mean that we endorse or approve third parties’ policies towards visitor privacy.

This simply means when you provide information in the course of obtaining third party products or services through our website, the use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those third party products or services, even if it appears that you are on iPraxa-branded pages throughout the transaction. The third party provider's privacy policy may differ from ours and you should contact the third party provider if you have any questions about its privacy practices. We also recommend you review the third party website’s privacy policy before you share any personal data with them.

### Opt-out, Delete or Modify Personal Information

You may opt-out of receiving any e-mails and/or SMS from us anytime. If you want to delete or modify your personal information, drop us an email at contact@ipraxa.com. We encourage you promptly to notify us to update your personal information if it changes.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small string of information that provides information regarding the computer used by a website visitor. We may use cookies to gather data about your computer and follow your activities on our website as this helps us better understand your preferences and accordingly improve our website experience for you.

As we mentioned earlier as well, any information we collect through cookies will not identify your personal details in any manner. It's just a statistical data. However, if you don't want us to save your personal information and preferences, you can turn off all cookies by adjusting adjust your browser settings, if you wish.

### Beacons

We, along with certain third parties, may also use beacons or pixels to collect information from your device to our server. Beacons or pixels can be embedded in online content, emails, and videos and permit the server to:

  * Read and collect certain types of information from your device
  * Know when you have viewed a particular content or email message
  * Determine the time and date on which you viewed the beacon
  * Store the IP address of your device

We, including certain third parties, use beacons for a variety of purposes, such as analyzing the use of our services and serving more relevant ads to our clients and visitors.

### Protection of Your Information

All information gathered on our site is stored within an iPraxa-controlled database accessible only to iPraxa.com and we endeavor our level best to protect your personally identifiable information against loss, destruction, unauthorized access, misuse, modification or distribution. However, as effective as any security measure may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We urge you to exercise caution from your end while transmitting any information over the Internet.

### Online Policy

This Privacy Policy does not describe the ways in which iPraxa may collect or use information obtained through means other than its website, iPraxa.com. It only applies to information collected through the website and not to information collected offline. Also, it does not extend to anything that is beyond our control and that is inherent in the operation of the Internet.

### Amendments to This Privacy Policy

Since we frequently update our Privacy Policy from time to time, we request you to check back this page often for any of the changes so that you can stay informed about the steps we are taking to protect your personal information. Thus, we are assuming that you acknowledge and agree that it's solely your responsibility to review this Policy regularly and become aware of any updates and modifications. This is the most recent version of our Privacy Policy. Please check the “effective date” mentioned at the top of the page to see when the Privacy Policy was last updated.

### Your Consent

If you are using our website, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy as well as to our Terms & Conditions. And, if you don't agree, please do not use iPraxa's website and do not provide us with personal information.

### Email Address for Privacy Questions

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or have doubts about our information collection, use, and disclosure practices, you can email us at contact@ipraxa.com. We’ll try our level best to respond promptly to any questions or concerns, which you may have regarding our use of your Personal Information.
